# Like Zheng

Software Engineer || Product Manager

☑ like@ekil.sh ☐ ekil1100 ☑ ekil1100 in likezheng

#### **About**

Hi, my name is Like Zheng. Throughout my 5-year career, I have spent the first 3 years as a software engineer and the latter 2 years primarily working as a product manager, with a decent understanding of UI design. In my spare time, I enjoy writing code and experimenting with new technologies. My expertise leans more towards front-end development as opposed to back-end, and I have a strong focus on user experience, which is why I've taken up learning about product design and UI design. I value teamwork and have successfully built a 6-member front-end team from scratch, fostering an agile culture along the way.

### **Experience**

ByteArk Tech Ltd.

2022年8月-现在

Community & Product Manager

Remote

Manage and compile information from the Filecoin community, as well as engage in the design of applications based on Filecoin.

- Designed and took part in the development of a Filecoin remote sealing (Sealing-as-a-Service) platform.
- Publish the internal Filecoin Weekly newsletter, which covers topics such as Filecoin-related news, events, code updates, articles, and videos. Successfully released 10 issues, accumulating views of over 200.

ByteArk Tech Ltd.

2021年8月-2022年7月

**Product Manager** Hangzhou, China

Led a team focused on developing applications based on Filecoin and IPFS.

- Managed a team of 5 people, including 2 Front-End Developers, 2 Back-End Developers, and 1 UI designer.
- Build a prototype of cloud storage application based on Filecoin and IPFS.

Muri Tech Ltd.

2021年3月-2021年7月

Front-End Lead Hangzhou, China

During the probationary period, assisted the team in optimizing Git workflow and advancing the development of design systems, leading to an early promotion to Front-End Team Lead.

- Led a 5-member front-end team, responsible for developing and maintaining web applications.
- Migrated code from UmiJS to NextJS and conducted refactoring, improving SEO, reducing package size by 10%, and enhancing the development experience.
- Developed Git workflow based on Trunk-Based Development and authored documentation.

ByteArk Tech Ltd.

2019年2月-2021年2月

Front-End Lead Hangzhou, China

Started as a Front-End Engineer and was promoted to Front-End Leader upon successful completion of the probation period. Spearheaded the establishment of the Front-End team, developing the team's development processes and standards.

Managed a team of 8 developers to develop web applications, mobile apps, and WeChat mini-programs.

- Established the team's development processes and standards, including Git usage guidelines, code review guidelines, and design system.
- Researched Agile development methodologies, implemented best practices to improve team performance, and produced over 10,000 words of documentation.

# Ningbo Port Information and Communication Ltd.

2018年8月-2019年1月

Front-end Developer

Ningbo, China

Efficiently developed and meticulously maintained a website for port declaration system using Java and ExtJS.

 Improved developer experience by incorporating polyfills for IE11, increasing browser compatibility and enhancing functionality.

## **Projects**

**Pandarua** 

2022年8月-2022年9月

Product Manager ByteArk Tech Ltd.

Figma Product Map

A Filecoin sealing-as-a-service platform.

· Designed the prototype.

**´MePrint** 2021年3月-2021年7月

Front-End Lead Muri Tech Ltd.

React NextJS React Query Emotion DirectusCMS

An Al-powered pattern design platform for the apparel industry.

- Refactored the codebase from UmiJS to NextJS using a progressive model, improving the developer experience (DX) and reducing the bundle size by 10%.
- · Managed application state using react-query, reducing bugs in global state management.
- Introduced a headless CMS to manage website content, making it faster and easier for operators to update the site.

**Dragonfly** 2020 年 10 月 - 2020 年 11 月

Product Manager & Front-End Lead

ByteArk Tech Ltd.

 Vue
 NodeJS
 Go
 Powergate
 IPFS
 Lotus

A decentralized docker image storage service developed as an entry to the Filecoin Slingshot Program.

- · Awarded Phase 1 first prize in the Filecoin Slingshot Program.
- Modified Powergate to support importing cold deals into its database.
- Presented the project at the Closing Ceremony, link available here: https://www.youtube.com/watch? v=qheNJZ1DCIM&t=1390s

**Matrix** 2019年9月-2020年1月

Front-End Lead ByteArk Tech Ltd.

Flutter Taro React Fastlane

A miner management system for Filecoin that includes a mobile app and WeChat mini-program.

- Built multi-platform mobile applications using Flutter.
- · Automated the release process using Fastlane.

٠.



2019年9月-2020年1月

Front-End Lead ByteArk Tech Ltd.

TypeScript React Rollup Emotion Storybook Jest

A design system focus on accessibility and usability.

- Researched over 10 design systems.
- Developed over 10 components and successfully launched in production.

### Education

# **University of Guelph**

2012年9月-2017年12月

Computer EngineeringBachelor

### Skills

NextJS ReactJS Front-end Senior JavaScript TypeScript Graphql Back-end Senior NodeJS PostgreSQL Prisma NextJS Graphql Mobile Intermediate Flutter Dart **DevOps** Intermediate Docker **AWS** AliCloud Vercel Serverless **Project Management** Intermediate Agile Scrum Linear **Design** Intermediate Figma

# Languages

Chinese Native speaker English Fluent

https://resume.ekil.io 2023 年 3 月 16 日 23:57:31